Finding aid for the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archive Collection of Audio Materials, 1970-1999 LSC.2230
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Groups Alphabetized by Group/Topic Cassettes, 1975-1995; Series 19.; 59 audio cassette tapes
  - Alix Dobkin: Lavender Jane Loves Women, 1973; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 6)
    Alix Dobkin is an American singer and songwriter. Side 1: Fantasy Girl, Quartet, Jo's B-Day Song, Charlie Beware, Talking Lesbian, A Woman's Love, View From Gay Head. Side 2: The Woman in Your Life, Caledonia, Yells, Eppie Morrie, Jovanno, I Only Want To Be With You, Little House, Her Precious Love
    Tape is unplayable.
  - Joanna Cazden: Rebel Girl, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 7)
    Recording of a live concert. Side 1: Full Moon, Empty Sky; The Woman in Front of the Bus; More Little Boxes; The Best of Intentions; Last Night I Had the Strangest Dream. Side 2: The Greatest Illusion, Rose City Ramble, I Walk the Hills, Close the Door, The Rebel Girl.
    Copyright 1984 Sister Sun Music
  - Reclaiming Community: Chants/Ritual Music, [ca. 1980s]; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 8)
    Chants and ritual music that are meant to be followed and repeated by listeners. Side 1: The Beginning of the Earth; Touching Her Deep; Air I Am; Rise with the Fire, Snake Woman; Goddess Medley: Isis Astarte; We Are an Old People; I Am a Strong Woman, We Are the Flow; Silver Shining Wheel; Where There's Fear There's Power; Hecate, Cerridwen. Side 2: Return to Mother, Born of Water, Air Moves Us, Water and Stone, We All Come from the Goddess, Kore Chant, We Are the Flow, Sun King, We Are Alive.
  - The Chenille Sisters: Mama, I Wanna Make Rhythm, 1991; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 9)
    Fourth album by the American contemporary folk band, which includes singer Grace Morand, guitarist and songwriter Connie Huber, and singer/songwriter Cheryl Dawdy. Side 1: Chocolate; La Bamba (An English Translation); A Change is Gonna Come; Roadmaps; Mama, I Wanna Make Rhythm; The Wind. Side 2 Sally's Advice; Is It True, Albert?; Hummin' To Myself; A Chill In The Air; I Am A Can Of Tuna, Big Hair.
    Copyright 1991 Red House Records
  - Cris Williamson & Teresa Trull: Country Blessed, 1989; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 10)
    Cris Williamson is an American feminist singer-songwriter and an open lesbian political activist. Teresa Trull is also an American singer-songwriter. Side 1: Keep On, Country Blessed, Calamity Jane, For Molly's Sky, The Love We Take. Side 2: Mother, Mother; The Shady Glen; Soulful Days; Fertanga.
    Copyrigh 1989 Second Wave Records
  - Pam & Maggie: Crazy For You!, 1989; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 11)
    Pam & Maggie are a songwriting and singing duo based out of Portland, Oregon. Side 1: I've Seen The Light, Friends To Lover, I Want To Be There, Faded Photographs. Side 2: Crazy For You, Doin' Like My Mama Done, Our Love, Grandma.
    Copyright 1989 Marguerite Beck
  - Deuce: Deuce, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 12)
    Duece band is Jean Finebers and Ellen Seeling, with Teresa Trull, Carol MacDonald, and Laura Theodore. Side 1: Partly Sonny, Smooth Move, Texas Pearl, No Pain, No Gain. Side 2: Blackout, Love Stings, Chevere, Watersounds, Bodybuilder.
    Copyright 1986 Deuce
  - The Fabulous Dyketones: Live in P-Town at the Town House, 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 13)
    Professional recording of live show. The Fabulous Dyketones performed 1950s recording hits in drag. Side 1: Everyday People; Rock Around the Clock; Rockin' Robin; The Fabulous Dyketones Theme Song; Ooh Baby, Baby; Why Do Fools Fall In Love; To Know Her Is To Love Her; Splish Splash; Be My Baby' La Bamba' She's So Fine; 16 Candles; Not Fade Away; I Heard It Through The Grapevine. Side 2: Funk-e; Da Doo Ron Ron; My Girlfriend's Back; Shout; The Blues in G; Breakin' Up Is Hard To Do; Somewhere (A Place For Us); I Can't Help Myself/Sugar Pie, Honey Bunch; Mony Mony; Goodnight, Well It's Time To Go; Crazy.
    Copyright 1988 Rock n'RolERecordings
  - Various Artists: A Family of Friends, 1993; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 14)
    A women's music sampler. Side 1: A Family of Friends, Heartland, Carry Me, At Karen's House, All Over Me, Linda, Happy Life. Side 2: The Kind of Woman I Am, Family (World of Love), On My Way, My Kind of Girl, Myth in Genesis, Lez-B-Bop.
    Copyright 1993 Tsunami Records, INC.
  - Sue Fink and Diane Lindsay: Tour 1985, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 15)
    Side 1: Crazy about you, Boys are thugs, Love won't let go, Open up. Side 2: An interview with Diane Lindsay and Sue Fink on KPFK FM Pacifica Radio (October 1984).
    Copyright 1984 Terre Music
  - Shaktivilas Chamber Ensemble: The Fire of My Love, 1976; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 16)
    "Songs for Gurumayi Chidvilasananda by the Shaktivilas Chamber Ensemble." Meg Christian, vocals, guitar; Katya Brown, cello; Shanta Brown, violin; Chris Williams, recorder; Bharadvaja Hamilton, Tablas. Side 1: The Fire of My Love, Would You Let Me Just Follow Behind, Darshan, Amazing Grace, Aisi Kari Shri Gurudeva Daya. Side 2: Amritanubhava, Gurumother, I Was Warned About The Flames of Love, Oh My Gurumayi
    Copyright 1976 Moogy Music
  - Kay Gardner: Fishersdaughter, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 17)
    Tape is unplayable. Side 1: "Sea" Fishersdaughter, Busker's Tune, Wind & Sea, The Ballad of Mary & Ann, The Banshee Song. Side 2: "Earth" Tyme-Robin Fre, Reminiscence-Diana Davies, Mother Mountain, Do You Remember? I Am the Earth.
    Copyright 1986 Even Keel Records
  - Various Artists: For Therese, 10 March 1990; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 18)
    Fifteen years of solo, vocal, choral, and instrumental music from Therese Edell. 60-minute recording or various artists performing Therese Edell's music on March 10, 1990 in Cincinnati, Ohio. For several years from 1978 through the mid-1980s, Therese Edell was the unofficial Voice of the Michigan Womyn's Music Festival. She was involved in every festival as a performer, sound engineer, or announcer since the second gathering in 1978. Audio recordings include Prophecy's Child (1970), From Women's Faces (1978), and For Therese (1990). Side 1: For Therese (Betsy Lippitt), Good Friends Are the Best, Texas Texas, Emma, Sister Heathenspinster's Calendar Days, Heart of Mine, Katie's Song, If you came here alone. Side 2: Holly's Waltz; Gather In; It's a Blue Moon; 38: 3 Sections, 8 Yrs; This Longest Night; O My Friends (Therese Edell and Lynn Herman).
    Copyright 1990 Sea Friends Recordings
  - Peggy Gilbert and the Dixie Belles: Dixieland Jazz, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 19)
    Peggy Gilbert, born Margaret F. Knechtges, was an American jazz saxophonist and bandleader. Side 1: Alexander's Ragtime Band, Boogie ala Georgia, Sweet Georgia Brown, A Closer Walk with Thee, When the Saints Come Marching In. Side 2: Jada, Georgia On My Mind, Struttin' with Some Barbecue, Back Home in Indiana
    Copyright 1986 Cambria Records
  - Girls in the Nose: Origin of the World, 1992; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 1)
    Girls in the Nose was founded in 1987 by Kay Turner and Gretchen Phillips (also in Two Nice Girls, Gretchen Phillips Experience), and is a band of six Austin-based women. Side 1: Medusa; Sodomy; These Hips; Sappho's Song; Hey, Chastity. Side 2: Breast Exam; Mode Madonna; Less Jesus; Incongruity; Pink Guitar.
    Copyright 1992 Girls in the Nose
  - Girls in the Nose: Girls in the Nose, 1990; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 2)
    Girls in the Nose was founded in 1987 by Kay Turner and Gretchen Phillips (also in Two Nice Girls, Gretchen Phillips Experience), and is a band of six Austin-based women. Side 1: Where Girls Go, Two Lovers/Two Altars, Meat, What Were You Saying, Menstrual Hut, Funky Slide. Side 2: Bite Me, Come and Die, Honorary Heterosexual Lesbian, Starpower.
    Copyright 1990 Girls in the Nose
  - The Guest Stars: Out At Night, 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 3)
    The Guest Stars were a jazz band, that celebrated defying sexual and gender norms. Side 1: Montezuma's Mother, Miles Apart, Amy's Bounce, What Means Love. Side 2: The Wind is Getting Angry, Song of the Bridge, Uranus in Jeopardy, Birds of a Feather.
  - Holly Near, Arlo Guthrie, Ronnie Gilbert, & Pete Seeger: HARP, A Time to Sing!, 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 4)
    Live recording of a 1984 concert that brought together Holly Near, Arlo Guthrie, Ronnie Gilbert, & Pete Seeger to perform songs by each artist and some cover songs. Side 1: Oh May Don't You Weep, Somos El Barco, City of New Orleans, Fine Time, All Over The World. Side 2: Small Business Blues, What's Going On, Foolish Notion, Wimoweh, Jacob's Ladder, Good For the World, Pallet on the Floor.
    Copyright 1985 Redwood Records
  - Heart: Heart, 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 5)
    American rock band led by sisters, Ann Wilson and Nancy Wilson. Side 1: If Looks Could Kill, What About Love, Never, These Dreams, The Wolf. Side 2: All Eyes, Nobody home, Nothin' At All, What He Don't, Shell Shock.
    Copyright 1985 Capitol Records
  - Jasmine: Wild Strings, 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 6)
    JASMINE was formed in 1978 by Carol Schmidt and Michele Isam. Side 1: Across the Wide; I Did My Part; Alla That's All Right, But I Depend on the Muses; How Smooth Goodbuys Can Be; Too Late. Side 2: Come On Home, Time Is Your Youngest Friends, Where I Belong Harriet Tubman, Whole Lot of Me, Wild Strings.
    Copyright 1987 Icebergg Records
  - Alix Dobkin: Lavender Jane Loves Women, 1975; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 7)
    Alix Dobkin is an American folk singer-songwriter. The album also features Kay Gardner. Side 1: The Women in Your Life, Caledonia, Yells, Eppie Morrie, Jovanno, I Only Want To Be With You, Little House, Her Precious Love. Side 2: Fantasy Girl, Quartet, Jo's B-day Song, Charlie, Beware, Talking Lesbian, A Woman's Love, View From Gay Head.
    Copyright 1975 Alix Dobkin
  - Lifeline: We Have Seen the Future, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 8)
    Side 1: Opportunity, Coming Into My Years, I Have Seen the Future, I'm Settled. Side 2: Harriet Tubman, Working Girl Blues/Nine to Five, Shooting Star, One's Who've Gone Before Us.
    Copyright 1983 Opportunity Enterprises
  - The Los Angeles Women's Community Chorus: 10th Anniversary Album, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 9)
    Recorded musical album in original packaging. Album liner notes, "This album was recorded at St. Augustine-by-the-Sea Episcopal Church, Santa Monica, California, Summer, 1986. Recording on location: Digital Brothers Newport Beach, California, Overdubs and Mixdowns: Frank Sullivan Studio, Pasadena, California. Side 1: Woman Spirit/Woman Strong, New Woman Rising, On Children, Aure Volante, Arms Open in the Night. Side 2: The Fury, La Andina, Days of Theocracy, Working Women's Medley
  - Rosario Marciano: Tailleferre, Chaminade, Anna Amalia, 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 10)
    Rosario Marciano was a Venezuela musician who combined performance, scholarship and teaching. Side 1: Tailleferre, Anne-Amalia. Side 2: Anna-Amalia, Chaminade
    Copyright 1980 The Moss Music group, INC.
  - Meg Christian & Cris Williamson: Meg/Cris at Carnegie Hall, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 11)
    The concert recording of Meg Christian and Cris Williamson at Carnegie Hall was a break-through for women's music. The genre was beginming to come into its own and be recognized. Women's music began to give feminists and lesbians a sense of belonging and an art form for expression. Side 1: Anniversary; Beautiful Soul; Can't Turn Back; Look Within; The One's Who Aren't There; Glad To Be A Woman; Train Song; So Good, So Right. Side 2: Soaring, Doin' Time, Texas Ruby Red, Light And The Eye, Come Hell Or High Water.
    Copyright 1983 Second Wave Records, INC.
  - Mignon: Fists to the Sun, 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 12)
    Mignon is a South African musician and activist, who performed at resistance concerts during the time of South African apartheid. She was also a leader in Johannesburg gay rights protests and pride parades. Side 1: Song of Exile, Here we go again, Sticks and Stones, Not a matter of love, Into the Light. Side 2: Stranger on the Wall, Sort this out (Woman to Woman), Communities, Patterns, The Struggle Continues.
    Copyright 1988 Pondok Records
  - Ruth Barrett & Cyntia Smith: Music of The Rolling World, 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 13)
    Ruth Barrett and Cyntia Smith are singers and songwriters, who specialize in playing the fretted dulcimer. The album music is inspired by myth, folklore, ancient symbolism, and the celebration of Nature. Their performances also include love songs, unique instrumental pieces and traditional folk music of the British Isles. Side 1: Unicorns, Sovay, I Live Not Where I Love, The French Dances, Faerie's Love Song, The Rolling World. Side 2: The Broomfield Hill, Pavan, The Weaver and The Factory Mail, Planxty Irwin/Lock Lovan Castle, The Cuckoo, Lovers of the Moon, Cambridge May Song.
    Copyright 1982 Aeolus Music
  - Janna MacAuslan & Kristan Aspen: Musica Femina, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 14)
    Kristan and Janna began playing as a duo in 1981. The music they play is focused on works written by women. Side 1: Bay Bridge, 6 Danses Pour Syrinx, Adagio (Sonata in F), New Beginnings, Zambra. Side 2: Suite for Solo Flute, Sicilienne, Five Pieces for Flute and Guitar.
  - Janna MacAuslan & Kristan Aspen: Musica Feminia, More Flute-Guitar Music by Women Composers, 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 15)
    Kristan and Janna began playing as a duo in 1981. The music they play is focused on works written by women. Side 1: Apryl Toye, Night Breezes, Caprice, Green Apple Rag, Minstrel I, Hearts of Silver. Side 2: Sonata in D, Sonatine Pour Flute Seule, A Sad Pavan Forbidding Mourning, Sonata for Three.
  - Somethin' Special Performance, 13 December 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 16)
    Recording of live musical performance. Spoken word is inaudible.
  - Holly Near & Ronnie Gilbert: Lifeline, 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 17)
    Holly Near is an American singer-songwriter, actor, teacher, and activist for social change. Ronnie Gilbert is an American folk singer. She is one of the original members of the Weavers with Pete Seeger, Lee Hays, and Fred Hellerman. Side 1: Harriet Tubman, Si Me Quieres Escribir, Beloved Comrade, Two Good Arms, Biko, Gracias A La Vida, Pastures of Plenty, Stormy Weather. Side 2: Goodnight Irene, No More Genocide, Isabel, Perfect Night, The Activity Room, Hay Una Mujer Desaparecida, Singing For Our Lives.
    Copyright 1988 Redwood Records
  - The ARS Femina Ensemble: Non Tacete! (I'll not be silent!), [ca. 1980s]; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 18)
    Music written by women before 1800. Side 1: Cari Musici motet, Sonata in A major, Lamento. Side 2: Sonata Quarta, La Tempesta, A false designe to be Cruel, Se pieta da voi non trovo, Suite from La Liberazione di Ruggiero.
  - Ova: Possibilities, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 19)
    Ova was part of the Stroppy Cow Records label, which was an independent feminist record label that encouraged women to make their own kind of music in their own time and space, without the counterproductive pressures of commercialism. Side 1: Travelling Spirit, The Granny Song, Language of Lovers, Earthquake. Side 2: Moving Inside, Tidal Dream, Far Beyond the Dawn, Happy Drumming, Possibilities.
    Copyright 1984 Ova Music
  - Fem 2 Fem: Where Did Love Go, 1995; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 20)
    Fem2Fem was a 1990s techno group who released two albums. They were the first openly lesbian pop group. Recording is a single, "Where Did Love Go," which includes the original mix, as well as the Bak2BASSiks 7" remix.
    Copyright 1995 Avenue Foch Records
  - Ova: Who Gave Birth to the Universe, 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 1)
    Ova was part of the Stroppy Cow Records label, which was an independent feminist record label that encouraged women to make their own kind of music in their own time and space, without the counterproductive pressures of commercialism. Side 1: Political Beings, Who Gave Birth to the Universe?, Jamie's Song, Solid Ground, Ruby Song. Side 2: Rainforest, See the Way Clear, Get Over You, Healing Touch, Abseil Away.
    Copyright 1988 Stroppy Cow Records
  - Rosario Marciano: Piano Works by Women Composers, 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 2)
    Rosario Marciano was a Venezuela musician who combined performance, scholarship and teaching. Only Side 2 is playable. Side 1: Jacquet de la Guerre: Rondeau; Paradis: Sicilienne; Szymanowska: Nocturne; Cibbini-Kozeluch: Six Valses; Mendelssohn: Prelude; Schumann. Side 2: Brosnart: Valse-Caprice; Backer-Grondale: Visnet; Ungdomssang; Carreno: Venise; Intermezzo-Scherzoso; Chaminade: Pas des Echarpes; La Lisonjeera; Tailleferre: Sicilienne; Beach: Improvisation; Bacewicz: Maly Tryptik.
    Copyright 1980 The Moss Music Group Inc.
  - Emer Buckley: Elisabeth Jacquet de la Guerre, Pieces de Clavecin (1687), 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 3)
    Side 1: Suite en re mineur, Suite en sol mineur. Side 2: Suite en la mineur, Suite en Fa majeur.
    Copyright 1982 Harmonia Mundi
  - The Redwood Collection: Selected Music from Redwood Records, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 4)
    Selected Music from Redwood Records, which was created by Holly Near in 1972. Artists Include: Holly Near, Arlo Guthrie, Ronnie Gilbert, Pete Seeger, Judy Small, Nancy Vogl, Guardabarranco, Inti-Illimani, Ferron, Mary Watkins, Linda Tillery, and Connie Kaldo.
    Copyright 1986 Redwood Records
  - Scenes from the Samurai Jungle, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 5)
    Produced and performed by Pauline Moore, Alicia Siegall, Stephen Morden. Side 1: Soliloquy, Samurai Samba, Soaring. Side 2: Full Moon Celebration, Fushigi, Dusty Sneakers.
  - Shaktivilas Chamber Ensemble: The Fire Of My Love, 1976; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 6)
    Side 1: The Fire of My Love, Would You Let Me Just Follow Behind, Darshan, Amazing Grace, Aisi Kari Shri Gurudeva Daya. Side 2: Amritanubhava, Gurumother, I Was Warned About The Flames of Love, Oh My Gurumayi
  - Holly Near and Ronnie Gilbert: Singing With You, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 7)
    Holly Near is an American singer-songwriter, actor, teacher, and activist for social change. Ronnie Gilbert is an American folk singer. She is one of the original members of the Weavers with Pete Seeger, Lee Hays, and Fred Hellerman. Side 1: Singing With You, Lucky to be Me, The Right Time, I Cried, Simply Love, In a Restaurant by the Sea. Side 2: Medley, Wouldn't You Rather, Hand Me Down My Jogging Shoes, Kid's Song, The New Underground Railroad, The Great Peace March.
  - Lisa Thiel: Songs of Transformation, 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 8)
    Songs and chants from Tibetan, Sikh, and Goddess sources. Side 1: We Come From the Stars, Candlemas Song, Lady of the Flowing Waters, She's Been Waiting, May the Circle Be Open, Earth Song, Ek Ong Kar. Side 2: Acchi Mantra, Song of Courage, Saruba Shakti Mantra, Padmasambhava Mantra, Krishna Govinda, Govinda Hari, Gopala.
    Copyright 1988 Lisa Thiel
  - Teresa Chandler and Karen Ripley: I Survived A Femme!, 1993; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 9)
    Side 1: D-Y-K-E, That's My Ex-Lover, Desperately Dunking, Tax The Rich, Drug of Choice. Side 2: I Survived A Femme, Squeezin' Yours, Show Me Where It Hurts, #1, Woman Go Where Woman Want.
    Copyright 1993 Ruby Network
  - Sweet Honey in the Rock: Sweet Honey in the Rock, 1976; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 10)
    Sweet Honey in the Rock is an all-woman, African-American a cappella ensemble. They are an American Grammy Award-winning troupe who express their history as women of color through song, dance, and sign language. Side 1: Sweet Honey in the Rock, The Sun Will Never Go Down, Dream Variations, Let Us All Come Together, Joanne Little, Jesus is my Only Friend, Are There Any Rights I'm Entitled to. Side 2: Going to See My Baby, You Make My Day Pretty, Hey Mann, Doing Things Together, Traveling Shoes, Sweet Honey in the Rock #2.
  - Syzygy: Syzygy, 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 11)
    Side 1: Wonder, Dana, Not Supposed To, Last Life, Syzygy. Side 2: State of the Union, Daily Grey, Sensible Shoes, Chevy Memories, Steps Like These.
    Copyright 1988 Callisto Productions
  - The Tacoma Women's Choir: The time is now..., 1978; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 12)
    Director Tara O'Neil founded the Tacoma Women's Choir with the intention of creating an environment of political and social activism. Side 1: Tzena, Two Good Arms, There Comes a Time, What if the Russians Don't Come?, Hwishu, Breaths, 12 Months of Ronnie, Talking Want Ad. Side 2: Harriet Tubman, On Children, Testimony, Bread and Roses, Hay Una Mujer, Singing for Our Lives.
  - Honor Moore, Margie Adam, Susan Griffin, Janet Marlow: Take Hands, Singing and Speaking for Survival, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 13)
    Side 1: Who Among Us?, A Woman Thinks About War. Side 2: Spuyten Duyvil, Woodland.
    Copyright 1984 The Watershed Foundation
  - Maryland Lesbians: Together, Proud, and Strong, 1993; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 14)
    Performance of "Together, Proud, and Strong" by women from across the United States.
  - Nancy Vogel: Fight Like the Dancer, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 15)
    Side 1: Till I'm Over Losing You; Myth of Love; The Wonder of Your Love; Oh, America; Mary Katherine. Side 2: Mercy Me, I'm Lonely Tonight; Fight Like the Dancer; If You Care; Tumbleweed; I Don't Know Why; Start All Over Again.
    Copyright 1986 BMI
  - Kit Walker: Wind Follows the Tiger, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 16)
    Kit Walker is recording artist. He plays new-age music and jazz. Side 1: The Swan, Zephyr, Seed/Blossom, Wind Follows the Tiger. Side 2: Harvest Dance, Fruit of the Fields, Emptiness in My Hands, Mountain Folk.
    Copyright 1983 Kit Walker
  - Wild Women Don't Have the Blues, 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 17)
    Ida Cox, with the Coleman Hawkins Quintet, featuring Poy Eldridge and Sammy Price, Milt Hinton, and Jo Jones. Cox composed the title song in 1924. It is well-known because of its strong feminist message. Original recording April 12 and 13, 1961 in New York City. Side 1: Wild Women Don't Have the Blues, Blues for Rampart Street, St. Louis Blues, Fogyism, Hard Times Blues. Side 2: Cherry Pickin Blues; Hard, of Lord; Lawdy, Lawdy Blues; Death Letter Blues; Mama Goes Where Papa Goes.
    Copyright 1981 Rosetta Records
  - Various Artists: An Historical Sampling of Women Composers & the Music (Middle Ages to the Present), 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 18)
    Side 1: La Musica, French Baroque Cantatas, Franz Schubert, Louise Reichardt, Fanny Mendelssoh Hensel, Nineteenth Century Nonets, Lili Boulanger, Alma Mahler, Flute Reflections. Side 2: Clarinet, Violin, Piano; Judith Lang Zaimont; Song Cycles for Soprano Plus, The New York Bassoon Quartet, Songs of American Composers.
    Copyright 1986 Leonard Productions, Inc.
  - Various Artists: An Historical Sampling of Women Composers & the Music (Middle Ages to the Present), 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 19)